# **CONSTANT DRUON**

FRONT-END ENGINEER - SUMMER INTERNSHIP

#### **DETAILS**

#### PHONE

+33 (0) 6 38 40 51 62

#### FΜΔΙΙ

constant.druon@student.junia.com

#### LINKS

LinkedIn

#### SKILLS

React

React Native

JavaScript

TypeScript

Java

HTML & CSS

Node.js

С

Swift

IT Project Management

Adobe Creative Suite

# LANGUAGES

French | Native speaker

English | Proficient (CAE)

Spanish | Intermediate

German | Learn on my own

### HOBBIES

Cycling - Club & Regional Competitions Swimming Web 3.0 and NFT Electronics (Arduino and Raspberry)

#### **PROFILE**

I am a 21 years old french student in Software Engineering. I have created and sold several projects to finance my studies since the age of 15. As a big fan of entrepreneurship and innovation, I co-founded my own startup during my studies.

I am looking for a 3 to 4-month internship as a Software Engineer in an innovative company from early May 2022

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Cofounder and CEO, Yoko

Lille, France

Feb 2021

I co-founded Yoko, a startup incubated at Euratechnologies, the largest startup incubator in Europe. *Technical Stack: React, React Native*, Typescript, *NodeJs*, *GraphQL*.

# Front End Developer, Marginals'Lab

Lille, France

Jan 2018 — Jan 2020

I developed websites and mobile applications to finance my studies. *Technical Stack: React, React Native, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Swift.* 

## Industrial placement, ArcelorMittal

Desvres, France

Jul 2018 — Aug 2018

I worked on the assembly line, assisted the mechanical engineer in the control room.

### EDUCATION

# **HEI Engineering schools**

Lille, France

Sep 2019 — Jul 2023

Computer science, AI & IoT. I take part in many projects as part of my studies, mainly in: Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and C.

# **Lassalle Preparatory classes**

Lille, France

Sep 2017 — Jul 2019

Two-year of undergraduate intensive course in applied mathematics, physics and computer science.

### COURSES

Divide and Conquer, Sorting and Searching, and Randomized Algorithms, Stanford University Online

Sep 2020 — Dec 2020